https://aibc.ca/privacy-policy/

MenuAboutOrganizationRegulatory AuthorityGovernanceProfessional Governance Act TransitionBoards & CommitteesAnnual MeetingInitiativesOpportunitiesStaffContact Us CloseRegistrationBecome an Architect AIBCArchitectsIntern ArchitectsArchitectural TechnologistsRetired ArchitectsArchitectural FirmsTemporary LicencesHonorary MembersProfessional MobilityAnnual Renewal ClosePrograms & ServicesPractice AdviceRFPs & CompetitionsContractsPost-Disaster Building AssessmentAIBC ClassifiedsMunicipal Matrix CloseProfessional DevelopmentContinuing Education System (CES)AIBC Courses & Professional DevelopmentRecognized Educational Provider Program CloseProtecting the PublicAIBC’s Regulatory RoleDoes Your Project Need An Architect?ComplaintsProfessional ConductIllegal Practice CloseNews & EventsNewsCalendarSignature Events & ProgramsArchitectural Walking ToursMediaAIBC 100 CloseResourcesAIBC ResourcesIndustry ResourcesChaptersAffiliates Close
Home / Privacy PolicyThe AIBC recognizes the importance of the security of your personal information. Please read this web site privacy policy carefully.
By using the AIBC web site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy.
1. What information do we collect when you visit the AIBC web site?
When you browse our web site, the following information is collected:
The IP (internet protocol) address of your internet service provider;
The web browser you use;
The pages you viewed; and
Your country.
No personally identifiable information is collected.
2. What do we do with the information we collect?
We use the information collected to analyze the use and performance of the AIBC web site, using Google Analytics and other tools, to help us improve the website. We do not use the information we collect to identify web site users.
3. Does the AIBC web site use cookies?
This web site uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the web site (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the web site and to compile statistical reports on web site activity.
You are able to choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Please note if you choose not to accept cookies, your experience at our web site may be limited and some features may not work as intended.
4. Do we disclose information to third parties?
We do not sell or trade personally identifiable information.
The AIBC will disclose personal information provided through the AIBC’s website, and/or IP addresses to third parties only where required by law or for regulatory or compliance purposes.
5. Third party links
The AIBC web site may contain links to third party web sites. Those third party web sites have their own separate privacy policies. This privacy policy only applies to the AIBC web site. You may want to read the privacy policy of each web site you visit to determine what information is collected about you. The AIBC assumes no responsibility or liability for the content or activity on third party web sites.
6. Changes
From time to time, the AIBC may make changes to this web site policy. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes to this page.
7. Questions
If you have any questions about this policy please contact the AIBC at communications@aibc.ca.
Architectural Institute of B.C.
